<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui='urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder'
	xmlns:g='urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui' xmlns:myui='urn:import:com.baovue.myhobbyproject.client.application.ui'
	xmlns:s='urn:import:com.baovue.myhobbyproject.client.application.soccer'>

	<ui:with field="res" type="com.baovue.myhobbyproject.client.resources.AppResources"/>
	<ui:with field="nameTokens" type="com.baovue.myhobbyproject.client.place.NameTokens"></ui:with>
	
	<g:HTMLPanel>
		<myui:Header></myui:Header>
		
		<div class="{res.style.container}">
		
			<div class="{res.style.leftcontent}">
				<div class="{res.style.imagecontainer}">
					<g:Image resource="{res.soccerImage}" altText="soccerImage"/>
				</div>
				<a class="{res.style.links}" href='#{nameTokens.getSoccerPage}'>Soccer</a>
				<p>The Elite Clubs National League (ECNL), the nation’s premier female youth soccer league, 
				has kicked off the Amazing Young Women™ campaign and its rally cry #BeautifulAmbition. 
				The campaign is a dynamic platform of online and local market activations that showcase and 
				celebrate female role models offering an aspirational focus for all female athletes and teens 
				as they prepare to be our next generation of leaders. The Amazing Young Women campaign is 
				calling on women of all ages to share their personal moments of #BeautifulAmbition and help 
				drive a movement that celebrates the power of what it is to be an elite female athlete today.</p>				
			</div>
			
			<div class="{res.style.rightcontent}">
				<div class="{res.style.imagecontainer}">
					<g:Image resource="{res.cookingImage}" altText="cookingImage"/>
				</div>
				<a class="{res.style.links}" href='#{nameTokens.getCookingPage}'>Cooking</a>
				<p>Cooking is one of the oldest of human activities. When human evolution was at the hunter-gatherer 
				stage, cooking was very simple -- kill something, throw it on the fire along with whatever vegetables 
				and fruits were found that day, and eat. Spices and cooking equipment were rather simple at that time 
				and there probably was not much variety in the average diet back then. Since those very early beginnings, 
				cooking has become almost an art form but still remains a fundamental part of our everyday lives. Although 
				many Asian cultures share the tradition of gathering the family or clan together to socialize or celebrate 
				over a big meal, the various cultures of Asia each developed their own ethnic cuisine through the 
				interaction of history, environment, and culture.</p>
	
			</div>
		
		</div>
				
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>
